{
    "id": "33e19ecd12cb45a885c5f2b8fb4fff97",
    "title": "Collective Nouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Our audience …………….. always been the affluent urban elite.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2c4d5f2e1cd24dee9425f52db9c01e05"
        },
        {
            "question": "The audience at the open-air stadium ………………… not as large as had been expected.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fb303c59555c46238bd87ef0e9e87a51"
        },
        {
            "question": "The audience …………………. enthralled by her performance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ee8283be2f8c490b8482d619484ef4b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Audiences throughout the world ……………….. been captivated by Chaplin’s films.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b519c8557a78400d97b2276babbd42fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "The public ………………….. stringent laws to deal with terrorists.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "wants"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81cfa5efb7b84d099a9cf1636a9345ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "The public …………….. not satisfied with the relief measures taken during the floods.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a99f442168f74216ac7e906b02d3517e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The team ………………… practising at the stadium.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fa96500d9075493ab763e21791bf2f14"
        },
        {
            "question": "The team ………………. for Australia tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is leaving",
                "are leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "993fb659c1594f14a8168fbb063e3bb1"
        },
        {
            "question": "A family with four children ………………. next door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "434ff943a1344911b2f22020ee782a3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "My family …………………. going to be there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4a91dcb25b6e4858a58c358bbf3061be"
        }
    ]
}